wall-st.net 2011-11-09

# Wall St » Privacy Policy

Privacy

At Wall-St.net, we take the privacy and security of our registered users and subscribers seriously. We are committed to protecting the personal information you choose to share with us. Accordingly, we have adopted the following privacy policy, based on the principles of notice, choice, access and security in the collection and use of all information regarding our customers and their activities at Wall-St.net and our related sites.

Collection of Information

Registration and subscription data are the only personally identifiable information that Wall-St.net seeks about you. This information includes your email address and, in some cases, your name, mailing address, telephone number or fax number.  
We collect no information about our users that is not supplied voluntarily through web forms or email. We may at times collect anonymous tracking information to gauge usage patterns and the popularity of specific areas of our sites. As with all other information, this information is kept confidential for use only by employees and contractors of Wall-St.net. 

Some of these data are collected through the use of cookies. Cookies may be deactivated by the user at any time through features available on your Internet browser. They are not required for any Wall-St.net site to function properly. Transparent gifs or pixels may occasionally be used for the same purpose, but these items gather no personal information and have no effect on how you view our sites or how you navigate the site. 

Wall-St.net ’s privacy policy does not extend to anything that is inherent in the operation of the Internet, and therefore beyond our control, and is not to be applied in any manner contrary to current law or government regulation.

Your Email Address  
All of our e-letters, alerts and special notices from our advisors and partners are sent only to those who have specifically agreed to our confirmed opt-in policy. We require recipients of email from Wall-St.net to confirm permission for the email address submitted to be included on our mailing list by responding to a confirmation email for verification. This ensures our users are properly subscribed with a working address and with the owner’s consent. Unsubscribe instructions are included at the bottom of each email. Some e-letter issues include advertising, clearly marked as such. 

By registering to receive our email from Wall-St.net , you also agree to receive email announcements and special offers from our partners. If you are a subscriber to our investment newsletters, you will also receive information regarding your newsletter author’s site and/or service. Occasionally, we may write to you at your email address with offers from carefully screened companies that offer products, services or information we believe may be of interest to you.

We neither rent nor sell your email address to anyone. Though we hope you gain value from the messages you receive, you can choose to opt out of receiving further messages by following the instructions provided at the close of each email. To opt out of receiving future messages, We will honor the change to your account preferences on , however we also advertise on many other Internet and email outlets. Therefore, you may see our advertisements in connection with other financial and investment-related websites and email outlets. We will ensure that they offer you the ability to opt out from their messages.

Enter your email address and receive our FREE report

We Will Send you your Breaking Report:  
The 3 Silver Stocks Getting Ready To Soar
